kbcafe.com 2012-10-03

# Privacy - kbcafe

KBCafe.com, Resumebay.net and Talk-sports.net, here-in referred to as simply KBCafe, are committed to protecting your online privacy while providing you with the most useful and enjoyable Web experience possible. While you can use many features of KBCafe anonymously, you are required to provide personal information to gain access to some of our premium content and services.

## How we collect and use personal information

We occasionally will send e-mail to notify you about important changes to the site, new services, and special offers from us. In addition to receiving e-mail announcements, you can also sign up for e-mail services.

If you enter a contest or respond to a promotion, we may ask for your postal address so we can notify contest winners and deliver promotional goodies. We occasionally may also send you postal mail to notify you about important changes to the site, new services, and special offers from us and select KBCafe partners. 

## How we protect your personal information

In addition to using the most secure technology available, we work tirelessly to make sure that we use any information you provide us only in ways you have approved. 

## How we use "cookies"

As you probably know, "cookies" are small pieces of information that some Web sites store on your computer's hard drive when you visit them. Like many other Web sites, KBCafe uses cookies to identify members so they don’t have to enter information upon each visit. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies but allow you to modify security settings so you can approve or reject cookies on a case-by-case basis. Even if you do not use cookies, you can still access all of the features on our site by logging in manually with each visit.

## What we provide to third parties

While KBCafe does not provide any third-party access to your personal information except to facilitate your own attempts to register with our partners or receive offers from select partners as mentioned elsewhere in this policy, we may provide third parties with aggregate statistics about our customers, traffic patterns, and related site information. This data reflects site usage patterns gathered during millions of customer visits to our Web site each month, but it does not contain behavioral or identifying information about any individual member unless that member has given us permission to share that information.

KBCafe uses a third-party advertising company to serve ads when you visit our sites. This company may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address, or telephone number) about your visits to our and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. In addition, we share Web site usage information about visitors to our site with this company for the purpose of managing and targeting advertisements on our sites. 

## Obtaining your consent

By using our Web site, you give KBCafe permission to collect information about the pages served to you as an anonymous user for the purpose of calculating aggregate site statistics. If you register at KBCafe, you authorize KBCafe to use information you provide to personalize the information we deliver to you and to use your demographic information when calculating aggregate customer data. As a registered user, you give KBCafe and our agents permission to send you e-mails related to the subscription e-mail services to which you subscribe and the Free Product Info topics you select.

If you are under the age of 18, you must not provide your name, e-mail address, or any other identifying information without the consent of your parent or guardian, or as otherwise provided for by applicable law.

Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

## Tell us what you think

KBCafe welcomes your questions and comments about our privacy policy. Please send e-mail to feedback@kbcafe.com.
